# Robert Wang

## Senior AI Developer

With 6 years of experience as an AI developer, extensive knowledge is applied in designing and implementing intelligent systems using various programming languages and machine learning technologies. Strong analytical and programming skills enable solving complex problems and developing optimized solutions. The ability to work collaboratively in a team environment is enhanced by high motivation and excellent interpersonal skills.



robertwang3129@gmail.com



Helsinki, Finland

#### **SKILLS**

C++

JavaScript

Python

Data Science

Artificial intelligence

Data Analysis

MERN Stack

Django

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

NLP

Computer Vision

ChatGPT

Keras

TensorFlow

PvTorch

Skill

#### **LANGUAGES**

**Fnalish** 

Professional Working Proficiency

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Al Research Assistant Kahoot!

10/2019 - 05/2021

Data Model Design

- Conducted research in the areas of machine learning and natural language processing
- Designed and implemented deep learning models using TensorFlow and PyTorch
- Assisted in developing software applications that utilized machine learning techniques to solve various problems, such as image classification and text mining

# Artificial Intelligence Programmer Celonis SE

10/2021 - 04/2023

The Arts of Artificial Game Tech Solutions

- Design and execute well-engineered, easy-to-maintain, reliable, and bug-free code for various company applications in collaboration with other AI engineers, data scientists, programmers, and software personnel
- Continuously improve gameplay by working with the existing code base and enhancing its different phases, including AI strategies, rules, and player-world interactions
- Coordinate all technical and developmental issues/risks identified during the process to the team of 10+ AI engineers to formulate and initiate appropriate course of actions to ensure the timely completion of the version upgrade
- Design, test, and deploy new artificial intelligence functionalities for 8 major projects of the company worth \$15K in total
- Author sophisticated and optimized codes for different games to boost the reusability of standard modules

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Computer Science(BCompSc) University of Turku

2010 - 2014

Courses

Computer science and AI field

#### **INTERESTS**

Reading

AI & Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Web Development

Turku